===========================================================
==== How to Sapien/Foundation =============================
===========================================================

Tilda key [~] opens a inline interface within the ingame window in Sapien
This can be used in combination with scripts to test them.

ff10_prototype has a few examples such as the testing of the longsword supply drops

Script:
(script static void test_longsword_drop ...)

Type "test_longsword_drop" and hit [Enter] to run the script

===========================================================

How to Make a Firefight map from Campaign (fast)

1.  Identify a area of a Campaign Map to Use.
2.  Load the Campaign scenario in sapien.
3.  Identify the BSPs within that Zone Set. IE. m10_010, m10_020, m10_000
    Use [ctrl] + [b] to change between zone sets
    Usually campaign maps label their zonesets with the bsps they used

4.  In foundation open both the firefight map scenario and the campaign mission scenario which
    the firefight map is from.
5.  In the campaign mission scenario under the "structure bsps" field use the drop down 
    and select one of the needed bsps.
6.  Copy the required BSPs over and insert/append them into the structure bsps field in the
    firefight map scenario until all required are added.
7.  Update the Zone Set "set_firefight" in the firefight scenario with the correct bsps. 
    Reference the checked boxes in the campaign scenario zone set.

8.  In foundation open both the firefight and the campaign map's _faux_lightmap.scenario_lightmap file.
9.  In the campaign map's lightmap file under the "lightmap BSP references" field use the drop down 
    and select one of the needed bsps.
10. Copy the required BSPs over and insert/append them into the lightmap BSP references field in the
    firefight map scenario until all required are added.
11. Double check that the file path of modified scenario lightmap file is under the "new lightmaps"
    field in the main firefight scenario file.

To Fix Map Lighting: Do Steps 8-11.
You should be now left with a new map but with prexisting firefight objects

1. In Sapien drag drop alls objects into the new map area

   Player Spawn Blocks: 1-5 Human 6-11 Elite 12-13 Human 14-15 Elite
   Trigger Volumes: Kill, Safe Zones, Garbage/Recycle Zones
   Health Pack, Grenade, and Ammo Crates
   AI Formations
   ...theres is a lot of objects but these are the most important

2. In Zones under the AI folder, create a new sur_zones within the map space.
   You can delete the existing one. Make sure to generate firing positions.
3. Update obj_survival with the new zones so AI can work.
   When clicking on obj_survival a screen pops up, this screen is basically AI guidance to move. 
4. Remove ONLY existing movement instructions within obj_survival.
5. Create new movement instructions within obj_survival.
   The draggable cube indicates where the AI is currently is.
   Arrows indicate the direction of movement the AI will take.
   Select zones in order to create a path of movement, keep it simple though.
6. Fine tune map objects and AI instructions
7. Done

===========================================================

Cant update/edit script data points IE. change its position in sapien?
In the main firefight scenario, In the "scripting data" field, 
For every phantom/fork in the "point sets" and under "points"
change the "structure bsp tag" to a current one used in zone set.

Without changing this to a BSP that is being currently used within the zone set, 
sapien prevents the script data points from being moved/edited

===========================================================
